37. Cyberbullying. With the Internet, our friends are nearby even when they aren't.
Unfortunately, while the Internet allows us to stay close to our friends, it can also make us more vulnerable to our enemies.
Bullying has always been a problem in schools. Big kids pick on smaller kids, rich kids make fun of poor kids.
But nowadays, kids are being bullied even at home, where they should be safe.
Cyberbullying, which means bullying people over the Internet, is a serious and growing problem.
And since the Internet is always on and always available, victims of cyberbullying can feel like nowhere is safe.
Cyberbullying often occurs on social media sites like Facebook and Twitter.
Bullies post cruel comments on their victims' pages or send them mocking or threatening messages.
Rumors spread quickly online, so it can be hard for victims to defend themselves.
Sometimes other people join in on the attacks.
People seem to be more willing to join in attacks online than they would be in person.
In the end, victims can feel as if their whole class or school has turned against them.
It's a very lonely and frightening feeling.
Studies show that over half of U.S. school kids have experienced bullying online.
Just one in ten of them will tell his or her parents about it.
And less than 20 percent of these incidents will be reported to the police.
Cyberbullying is very dangerous.
There have been several instances of teenagers committing suicide because of it.
It is also largely invisible, which makes it hard to identify and even harder to stop.
Many countries have passed laws against cyberbullying.
Whether these laws will help end this crime for good remains to be seen.